CAMERON MALFARA

General Contractor with 5+ years of experience overseeing commercial construction projects.

Consistently achieve project goals, deadlines, and budget requirements. Combine strong leadership skills with extensive hands-on construction experience. Highly adaptable to new work conditions, finding quick and practical solutions to project challenges.

123 Windermere Rd., Seattle, WA 12345 yo u remai I @exa m p I e.com (123)456-7890

WORK EXPERIENCE

GENERAL CONTRACTOR

ABC Construction Consulting, Inc., Seattle, WA April 2020 to Present

- construction firm
- Coordinate with other project stakeholders, including vendors, engineers, and architects

Schedule and guide on-time delivery of complex projects for this commercial

- ♦ Hire and oversee subcontractors, ensuring consistent work quality and efficiency
- Maintain utmost job site safety and legal compliance

GENERAL CONTRACTOR

XYZ Construction Corp., Seattle, WA April 2017 to April 2020

- Managed all stages of commercial construction projects
- Addressed and resolved any project delays or constructability challenges
- ♦ Gained strong foundational knowledge of management and leadership principles

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN CONSTRUCTION MANAGEMENT

University of Washington, Seattle, WA, 2013 -2017

KEY SKILLS

- Budgeting & Cost Accounting
- Building Codes
- · Complex Problem-Solving
- · Contract Interpretation
- Cost Red uction & El i m i n ation
- Cross-Functional Collaboration
- Materials Procurement
- Project Man agem e n t
- · Regulatory Compliance
- · Staff Hiring
- · Stakeholder Relations
- Structural Modification
- Su bcont ra ctor M a n agemen t
- · Team Leadership
- Technical Drawings
- WorkPlanning&Scheduling
- Workplace Safety

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- ♦ Microsoft Excel
- ♦ Microsoft Project
- Procore
- ♦ Red Team